module.exports = [
  {
    question: 'According to Mr. Owl, how many licks does it take to get to get to the Tootsie Roll center of a Tootsie Pop?',
    a: '9000',
    b: '3',
    c: '50',
    d: '1',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is NOT a cryptocurrency?',
    a: 'Ethereum',
    b: 'Tron',
    c: 'Litecoin',
    d: 'Digimon',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'Who played Dorothy in the Wizard of Oz from 1939?',
    a: 'Judy Garland',
    b: 'Katharine Hepburn',
    c: 'Bette Davis',
    d: 'Veronica Lake',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'The "clavicle" is another name for what bone?',
    a: 'Collar',
    b: 'Shin',
    c: 'Tailbone',
    d: 'Hip',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: '"Zip-a-Dee-Doo-Dah" is a song from what Disney movie?',
    a: 'Br\'er Rabbit',
    b: 'Alice in Wonderland',
    c: 'The Jungle Book',
    d: 'Song of the South',
    answer: 'd'
  },
  {
    question: 'What fashion model was struck in the face by a goose while riding a rollercoaster at Busch Gardens?',
    a: 'Gisele Bundchen',
    b: 'Fabio',
    c: 'Cindy Crawford',
    d: 'Tyson Beckford',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'Andrew Carnegie made his fortune in which industry?',
    a: 'Steel',
    b: 'Oil',
    c: 'Automobiles',
    d: 'Telecommunications',
    answer: 'a'
  },
  {
    question: 'What type of animal would you find on a bottle of Jagermeister?',
    a: 'Fox',
    b: 'Stag',
    c: 'Bear',
    d: 'Goose',
    answer: 'b'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is a "Chimenea"?',
    a: 'A chimney damper',
    b: 'A beetle',
    c: 'A freestanding frireplace',
    d: 'A fish',
    answer: 'c'
  },
  {
    question: 'Rowan Atkinson is best known from his role as ____',
    a: 'Mr Bean',
    b: 'Ali G',
    c: 'Pee Wee Herman',
    d: 'Borat',
    answer: 'a'
  },
];
